<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Activity Report on Hafizulloh Ergashev</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/activity-report/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Activity Report on Hafizulloh Ergashev</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/activity-report/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cybersecurity: Attack and Defence in the Era of AI</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blogs/cybersecurity-attack-and-defence-in-the-era-of-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blogs/cybersecurity-attack-and-defence-in-the-era-of-ai/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I attended a webinar that brought together cybersecurity and AI experts to discuss the evolving threat landscape as artificial intelligence becomes increasingly integrated into business operations. The discussion has shown, that while AI introduces new attack vectors and challenges, many fundamental cybersecurity principles are still applicable. Key themes included the knowledge gap between data scientists and security professionals, governance requirements, and the inadequacy of current regulatory frameworks to keep pace with the growth of technologies, including AI.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Al and Machine Learning in Criminal Investigations: Opportunities and Challenges</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blogs/ai-and-machine-learning-in-criminal-investigations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blogs/ai-and-machine-learning-in-criminal-investigations/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On 6 May 2025, I attended a webinar &amp;ldquo;AI and Machine Learning in Criminal Investigations&amp;rdquo;. It was presented by Katharine Pearson. In the webinar an overview of the historical development of AI, its current applications in law enforcement, the ethical issues it raises were discussed. This report examines the potential uses of AI in policing, bias and privacy challenges, and the future of AI-driven investigations. Based on insights from the webinar, this report explores how AI can improve the criminal justice system while considering risks.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
